buysellwebsite.com 2010-03-29

# Privacy Policy for BuySellWebsite a Web Business Properties Inc Company

**Privacy Policy for BuySellWebsite.com** sm ****   
a Web Business Properties, Inc. company

> Privacy Policy   
>  Effective on: 7/24/04   
>  Last Revision: 04/26/09
> 
> Welcome to BuySellWebsitetm! BuySellWebsite.com®  provides its service to you, subject to the following Privacy Policy. 
> 
> BuySellWebsite.com® strives to follow fair and ethical business principles and our goal is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site WWW.BUYSELLWEBSITE.COM. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices.
> 
> If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact JC Phillippon at  [ jc@buysellwebsite.com](mailto:jc@buysellwebsite.com) or by mail at 2301 IL Route 26 N Freeport, IL 61032.
> 
> ** Information Collection & Use  
>   **
> 
> Send-a Page-to-a-Friend  
>   
> 
> If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address.  This referral service is handled by [ ConstantContact.com](http://www.constantcontact.com/) and will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.  BuySellWebsite.com® does not store this information.  
>   
> 
> Special Offers and Updates
> 
> We will occasionally send you information on new Website For-Sale Listings and infrequent promotions via email.  Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out.” 
> 
> Newsletters If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you.  Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.   
>   
> 
> Website For Sale Listings
> 
> When you fill out the form for listing your internet business for sale, that information is automatically posted to our public database of websites for sale.  All information you provide is freely available to anyone with the exception of your password.  This information includes your name, business name, email, phone, postal address, business description, ad headline, net income, total revenue, business start date, password, url, unique visitors, reason for selling, financing, employees, and asking price.
> 
> When payment is made for listings you are directed to a third party processor and any information given is only used for the purpose of completing that one time purchase.  This information is then shared back to BuySellWebsite.com®  for the purpose of completing your transaction.
> 
> Appraisals
> 
> The information we collect during the website appraisal process is held strictly confidential.  We only release information about you and your business with your permission first, either written or oral.  The information collected includes your name, business name, url, email, phone, postal address, business description, password, net income, and total revenue.
> 
> Affiliate  
>   
> 
> When signing up for our affiliate program you will be directed to [MyReferer.com](http://www.myreferer.com/), a third party that manages our affiliate program.  No data is shared with this affiliate management company. BuySellWebsite.com® retains all ownership of the information collected.  Information collected includes, name, url, email, password and postal address.
> 
> Service-related Announcements
> 
> We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.  For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.  It is not possible to opt-out of these messages.
> 
> Customer Service
> 
> Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password.  We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.
> 
> ** Information Sharing and Disclosure**
> 
> Personally identifiable information:
> 
> We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information in ways other than disclosed in this privacy statement.  Any information submitted to the Website For Sale Marketplace, Start-Up Marketplace and Miscellaneous Marketplace are considered public information because your contact information is listed in the listing. “You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you post there can be read, collected, or used by other users of this directory, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.  We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.
> 
> Service Providers
> 
> We use [PayPal](http://www.paypal.com/)[®](http://www.paypal.com/) to facilitate our payment processing. When you make a payment, you will be automatically transferred to PayPal's site. Please be aware that their privacy policy governs the use and collection of the information and some of this information is shared back with BuySellWebsite® to enable us to fulfill your order.   We also use [MyReferer](http://www.myreferer.com/), a third party, to manage our affiliate program. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.
> 
> Legal Disclaimer
> 
> We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site
> 
> Choice/Opt-out
> 
> If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication sent to you or by emailing us at [ buysell@buysellwebsite.com](mailto:buysell@buysellwebsite.com).
> 
> Access to Personally Identifiable Information
> 
> If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update or delete your listing by logging into your account by browsing to your ad and clicking on “Modify Your Ad” or by emailing our Customer Support at  [ buysell@buysellwebsite.com](mailto:buysell@buysellwebsite.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.
> 
> To delete your listing simply browse to your ad and click on “Modify Your Ad” and login, then select the delete button at the bottom of the page to permanently delete your listing.
> 
> Log Files
> 
> As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 
> 
> We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 
> 
>   
>  We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.  IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to authenticate transmissions submitted on forms. 
> 
>   
>  Cookies  
>  A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on our site to track who submits what information.
> 
> We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies.  We use session cookies to track advertising effectiveness. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.
> 
> We set a persistent cookie to track links sent to us by our affiliates.  If you reject cookies, you may still use our site.  This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by BuySellWebsite.com only.
> 
>   
>  Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)
> 
> Our third party advertising partners, both Overture and Google, employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information to help us better target our advertising.
> 
> To learn more about our advertising company’s use of clear gifs, please go to Overture.com and Google.com
> 
> We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients.  This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Choice and Opt-out.”
> 
> Security
> 
> We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. However, our payment processor, Paypal, uses SSL encryption to secure payment transmission.
> 
> Changes in this Privacy Statement  
>   
> 
> If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 
> 
> We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
> 
> Contact Us 
> 
> If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 800-564-2749 [ buysell@buysellwebsite.com](mailto:buysell@buysellwebsite.com) or by mail at  North Route 26, #2301, Freeport, IL 61032  
>  *BuySellWebsite.com is a business of Web Business Properties Inc, a Corporation in good standing in the state of Illinois, USA .  Web Business Properties Inc has been formed in the State of Illinois, and BuySellWebsite(tm) is a federally registered trademark.
